<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-07-09T22:13:56-06:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Kipukas</title><subtitle>Welcome to the Kipukas Card Binder! Here you will find all of the cards that make up Kipukas as well as some important info regarding game play. This site will remain free (as in beer) to use always as it is intended to enhance the game experiance, not lock you into a pay to play system. Our online shop is in active development at kipukas.us where you can find more info and make purchases. If desired, you can always email us with issues or order requests. Enjoy the site!</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Illia and Dorsay the Buck Skull</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/illia_and_dorsay_the_buck_skull/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Illia and Dorsay the Buck Skull" /><published>2024-07-04T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-07-04T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/illia_and_dorsay_the_deer_skull</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/illia_and_dorsay_the_buck_skull/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="bat" /><category term="wings" /><category term="deer" /><category term="skull" /><category term="trees" /><category term="jungle" /><category term="creepy" /><category term="scythe" /><category term="marsh" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Illia grew up a very sick child, barely surviving from year to year. She was constantly subjected to aggressive treatments, both well known and experimental. The experience left Illia no stranger to pain and misery. Out of desperation, her parents opted to have Illia undergo an experimental gene manipulation. While the procedure went as expected, Illia did not take to the manipulation and soon after passed. She was buried under ceremony and mourned, and ultimately left to her slumber. Dorsay grew up a fawn like any other. He learned to graze, listen and watch for predators, traverse rough lands, and how to compete for the affection of does. He did not take to one of those lessons well, and met an early demise. His carcass was left to the scavengers of the forest to devour and clean. Dorsay was left in his state, a pile of bones, for a fair number of years. Illia, on the other hand, was not resting as well. Even in her state, she continued to grow, mature, and mutate. Her grave had become a cocoon, containing the spirit to eventually emerge. She awoke in a panicked state, her back mashed against the rotted boards which once made up her coffin and her face smothered in dirt. Only able to make the smallest of movements, she moved the earth bit by bit until a tunnel barely large enough for her teenaged body emerged. Arduously, she moved the tunnel steadily upward until the ground became weak enough that to break through to the surface. She emerged like a creature from a horror scene mucky from her years underground, bloody from and splintered from rubbing against her coffin, and wearing the nearly completely deteriorated and much too small cloths she carried with her from her youth. Laying crumpled on the ground half out of the hole, Illia felt a soreness between her shoulders and reach back to rub the offending spot. She emitted a loud shriek when she realized the spot was no ordinary pain. Illia was now donning a set of skin covered wings. Despite her now monstrous appearance, she still carried the heart and soul of the sweet sickly little girl who was declared deceased. She wanted to go home, but knew not where home stood. She didn't know how to get there, she couldn't remember her address, and she wouldn't know who waited in stead. Also, she realized her horrific appearance would not garnish many friends. So, she ran and hid in the nearby woods to become a local myth. The creature lurking in the shadow, stealing food from the mouths of children, and pulling lost souls underground to make them like it. Of course, these stories were imbued with various levels of exaggeration. Lurking in the shadows was pretty true, Illia was too timid to be close to visitors of the woods. She certainly did steal food, but not literally from anyone's mouth. However, pulling souls into the underworld came from one unfortunate instance where a birder walked on top of her lose soil bed and felt an her arm grab his leg. It seems Illia became too comfortable sleeping underground. Still, these events were enough to peak the interest semi-local crypto-zoologists. Given their habit of chasing indefinite creatures, the hunt for what was essentially a little girl did not last long. After so long Illia ended up in a familiar and dreaded place, a hospital. This hospital was dedicated to medical research facility looking into her not so fatal experience all the while trying to contain any rumors of walking dead roaming the forest. They treated her as somewhat inhuman, not listening anor believing her memories or explanation. They assumed she was a creature smart enough to pick up human speech patterns, but not actually of our creed. Still, they eventually figured out the mutation sequence induced into her genes and reverse engineered it. Her existence on its owned posed a question for the scientists, how permanent is death. So, they began to further mutate the gene and test it on medically dead creatures with unsustainable success. The animals would animate for a short time then rapidly deteriorate back into abyss. During these studies the measured against several levels of dead, ranging from a few minutes of death to one particularly dry deer skull all the while subjecting Illia to increasing invasive tests. Well, Illia was done with her confines. She was done with the prodding. She was done being in a place she loathed. Illia had set her sights on escape. With a well timed bite on an unsuspecting orderly, she made a ferocious dash for the exit. Using every bit of her discharm to frighten any individual willing to stand between her and freedom. While generally effective, some hospital staff sought to prove their masculinity by catching the escaping beast and impeded Illia's progress forcing her to alternate between hiding and influencing terror. Here she meet Dorsay, as well as a larger than normal stash of dead rats. She stole him, putting Dorsay on her head hoping to make the staff think the stress furthered her freakish state. The rats too were stollen, all of which were thrown at a plethora of staff. Illia eventually reached a low enough story of the hospital to break a glass window, and find in her the courage to jump. Feeling the breeze pound against her face, she now thinks of the wings she previously despised as the wings she rode to freedom. After this ordeal, Illia and Dorsay disappeared fully from their birth local. Still, people around the planet say they hear whispers from underground and above when they visit the densest forests of the region. Mutters of the conversations between Illia and here friend Dorsay.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tears for Oly</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/tears_for_oly/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tears for Oly" /><published>2024-07-04T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-07-04T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/tears_for_oly</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/tears_for_oly/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sky" /><category term="city" /><category term="ancient" /><category term="rainbow" /><category term="colorful" /><category term="wing" /><category term="halo" /><category term="flow" /><category term="blonde" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many great civilizations have been built. Of these most, if not all, fall from grace in one aspect or another eventually to be torn down, or captured by means of force, coercion, or conviction. Each civilization carries a spirit of its people that becomes severed in the demise of the people. Oly, one such spirit, carries the burden of the memory and tragedies inflected upon his birth place. He dons cloth representing the fluidity of his culture, a golden bracelet and anklet representing the bindings of his ruler, and bares a golden vine symbolically pulling him from the heavens to the place of his creation. Oly's power steams directly from the influence of his society, which has largely been forgotten. So, he gives of him self the woe and tear for drink. Slowly draining the essence of himself and the last hope of his people, in a desperate attempt to dredge up their life for the memory of modern peoples. Doing this, he is wholly aware of the possibility of giving into his own demise.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tira Marvelous Myriad</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/tira_marvelous_myriad/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tira Marvelous Myriad" /><published>2024-07-04T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-07-04T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/tira_marvalous_mirad</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/tira_marvelous_myriad/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sky" /><category term="hands" /><category term="build" /><category term="machine" /><category term="wand" /><category term="red" /><category term="industrial" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tira is one of many mechanics employed to build and maintain high atmosphere launch platforms connecting to blue-red shift columns close to Kipukas space. Tira is exemplary, however. Not only does she take it upon her self to learn the complete plans of a project before execution, but she obsessively tailors her personal gear to fit its most miniscule details. This has resulted in a vast collection of fantastic devices which she employs with marvelous skill. As she works, the movements between her body and gear blend flawlessly. Whether positioning herself precariously to reach the bolt that no one else is daring enough to fasten, unabashedly jumping from scaffold to scaffold to be the first on the next project (or in the lunch line), or fending off would be pirates she presents a kind of intangible grace. Because of this, her colleagues often say she is an angel with talent instead of wings.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Gray Wolf: Harbinger of Night</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/gray_wolf_harbinger_of_night/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Gray Wolf: Harbinger of Night" /><published>2024-06-07T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-06-07T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/gray_wolf_harbinger_of_night</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/gray_wolf_harbinger_of_night/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="wolf" /><category term="howling" /><category term="forest" /><category term="rock" /><category term="edge" /><category term="cliff" /><category term="moon" /><category term="night" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Living on most of the world's continents, wolfs have fascinated people for centuries adapting their way into our hearts and homes. While most zoologists know the wolf's howl as a means of communication among their pack, some decided this was not enough. They sought to create the god our ancestors imagined them to be, gods of the night under the moon. Unlike normal gray wolves, these fervently praise the moon with their howls, thereby raising their collective mental state in exultance.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hidden Portal of Lower Dreadmont Cave</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/hidden_portal_of_lower_dreadmont_cave/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hidden Portal of Lower Dreadmont Cave" /><published>2024-06-07T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-06-07T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/hidden_portal_of_lower_dreadmont_cave</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/hidden_portal_of_lower_dreadmont_cave/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="cave" /><category term="mystical" /><category term="skull" /><category term="dragon" /><category term="explorer" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hiding deep within caverns of Dreadmont exists a gateway whence great power dwells. Few creatures have the means to survive the journey through the disorienting web-work passages, the ensnaring crevices, and sudden cliffs to reach the lower cave system. In the lower system there are fewer passages to follow, but horizontal points of rest become scarce. New treacherous obstacles such as rarified air displaced by toxic gases and water filled chambers join the effort to stave off explorers. Somewhere, miles below the surface, stands a tall cavern normally waiting in pitch black. However, when a skilled spelunker finds the cave with a heart open to receive the power and consequence dwelling beyond, a searing light emerges. Should the weary soul pass the final life binding test, they will find themselves past through the gate in a state beyond contestation.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Myrthvither Raven</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/myrthvither_raven/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Myrthvither Raven" /><published>2024-06-07T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-06-07T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/myrthvither_raven</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/myrthvither_raven/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="raven" /><category term="plant" /><category term="flower" /><category term="thorns" /><category term="crow" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Myrthvither Raven is a constantly moving and easily adapts to new environments. It possesses a wicked intelligence and tends to be quite self serving. Often, these ravens know several languages and can effectively communicate between species. Imbued with foliage near death, they easily disguise themselves in natural environments. They act as nearly perfect scouts, if offered a strong enough incentive to put themselves at risk. Many request exotic ant species as payment. Their intent with this behavior is unclear, however, some have observed ants living within their plant mass, a likely sign of a symbiotic relationship.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Neural Network Synapse Virus</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/neural_network_synapse_virus/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Neural Network Synapse Virus" /><published>2024-06-07T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-06-07T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/neural_network_synapse_virus</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/neural_network_synapse_virus/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="node" /><category term="block" /><category term="brain" /><category term="synapse" /><category term="computer" /><category term="lines" /><category term="web" /><category term="neuron" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of a class of virus designed to infect and interrupt the neural network. Subtle in design and task, the synapse virus is designed to inject itself from an infected host network into a model in training. By applying slight changes to the matrix, the virus undercuts the sensical responses an AI provides in response to environmental input. This virus has no meaning of existence.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Enchantress of Cats</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/enchantress_of_cats/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Enchantress of Cats" /><published>2023-12-21T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2023-12-21T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/entrantress_of_cats</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/enchantress_of_cats/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="cave" /><category term="cats" /><category term="witch" /><category term="old" /><category term="lady" /><category term="fire" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many have heard the rumors. Some have seen the fearsome creatures, but few have survived when met ankle to face with the black cat. Still fewer are those born to charm, entertain, and serve the spirits within. Among these leagues are those so in tune with the beasts that they win the beasts acclaim, no that's too strong, tolerance. These enchantresses even force the creatures to mind, sorry no, occasionally sway their opinion of what needs to be done. If you have experience with these creatures, you know the terror the enchantresses must inflict to get that type of response. Meow... ahhh!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Losetany Steppes</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/losetany_steppes/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Losetany Steppes" /><published>2023-12-21T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2023-12-21T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/losetany_steppes</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/losetany_steppes/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="jellyfish" /><category term="landscape" /><category term="camp" /><category term="yurt" /><category term="cloud" /><category term="night" /><category term="wonderer" /><category term="ruins" /><category term="statue" /><category term="mountains" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This kipuka contains many expansive grasslands and wastelands. For the people living here, it is considered a right of passage to survive a journey carrying their village token to the wizened elder. To complete their task they must face a walk through endless miles of grasslands, followed by a guided crossing beyond the regions tallest peak, and finished with a 3 day trek trough the wastes. After setting out with unsure glee, one of the tribe's young girls, Doran, just completed the first leg of her journey after finding the guide's camp near calumniator ruinas. Almost as a sign of her inevitable success, a bloom of the Cumulon jellyfish fills the night sky. Their waving lappets give Doran the sense that the creatures want to greet her into the the next chapters of her life. As she looks upon the glowing wisps of vapor, calm and reassurance wash over Doran. Now she can prepare for the next difficult steps of her journey.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ushered Through Sabina Emporium</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/ushered_through_sabina_emporium/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ushered Through Sabina Emporium" /><published>2023-12-21T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2023-12-21T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/ushered_through_sabina_emporium</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/ushered_through_sabina_emporium/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="crowd" /><category term="dragon" /><category term="skeleton" /><category term="manner" /><category term="shop" /><category term="mall" /><category term="detailed" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A battle between ancestry and heritage rages. In attempts to prove their hold on the future, fathers and sons spill the blood of each. The knowledge of what builds the future, our present, dissipates from the warriors' conscious. In its place rises the focus to triumph, skewing the edges of internal right and wrong. Before the future is lost to those with brave and foolish hearts, angels intervened with pleas for mercy. Selflessly running between the projectiles, their wives and daughters had called back the warriors' hearts to reality. The first daughter to demonstrate her courage, Sabina, died under bloody cloth. In her honor, a temple and a steeple were constructed upon the spot of her death. As often happens to grand buildings over the passing times, they become repurposed to suit the modern culture. In this case, Sabina's temple found bustling life as it transformed to its region's largest emporium. While luring to tourists, the emporium proves a glorious nest for scammers and thieves. Some find hidden jewels, archaeological treasures, or historical tomes while others find rubbish, malice, and sometimes death. Still, It has been said that when one casts their gaze to the sky beyond the vaulted glass they will feel overwhelmed with the courage of Sabina.]]></summary></entry></feed>