<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2026-02-25T22:16:47-07:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Kipukas</title><subtitle>Welcome to the Kipukas Card Binder! Here you will find all of the cards that make up Kipukas as well as some important info regarding game play. This site will remain free (as in beer) to use always as it is intended to enhance the game experiance, not lock you into a pay to play system. Our online shop is in active development at kipukas.us where you can find more info and make purchases. If desired, you can always email us with issues or order requests. Enjoy the site!</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Unburdened Central</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/unburdened_central/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unburdened Central" /><published>2024-09-20T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-09-20T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/unburdened_central</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/unburdened_central/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="mohawk" /><category term="crazy" /><category term="cyber" /><category term="punk" /><category term="wires" /><category term="cables" /><category term="holographic" /><category term="screen" /><category term="goggles" /><category term="glasses" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aurora 'Rory' Gale stood anchored to her workstation, a cyber welding rig of immense infrastructural expanse across the entire acres wide station, as she gazed up at the labyrinthine tangle of NeuroScape's physical infrastructure. Another grueling shift was winding down, but the endless stream of diagnostic alerts refused to cease. As a Tier3 Operator for omniHolo Innovations, Rory's role was to manually splice, repair, and reboot the antiquated yet crucial hardware supporting the company's proprietary SpineNet, the backbone of the post modern internet. The air reeked of burnt circuitry and desperation. omniHolo's bean counting reluctance to upgrade the physical systems had turned her job into a never ending game of whack-a-bug. Rory's arms, clad in a tight fitting, reinforced, feed-forward smart-assist enabled holoSuite, the latest ominHolo attempt to eke out just a few more tenths of labor efficiency, moved with precision. Rory's every move now felt guided by the whims of the holographic overlays dancing across her field of vision. She had lost count of the number of times she'd patched up the same frail junctures, only for them to fail again under the crushing load of global data traffic. After all, every move you make online costs someone Watts. SpineNet's virtual architecture was a marvel, but its physical foundation was a creaky, hack job relic. omniHolo's executives preached about 'prolonged system lifespan' and 'optimized maintenance costs,' while Rory bore the brunt of their frugality. Each spark that flew from her welding torch seemed to ignite a fresh ember of frustration within her. A particularly vicious alert shrieked through the comms system, signaling yet another catastrophic failure in the 4D. Rory's response was immediate, but her movements felt mechanical, fueled by simmering resentment rather than focus. As she worked to bypass the faulty module, a thought crystallized: How many more times? The question detonated something within her. With a fierce cry, Rory hurled her welding torch aside, its glowing tip skittering across the floor. She then began to yank out bundles of wires and cables. Don't dare think she did not know what she was doing, oh no. With every pull, she surgically extracted the crucial l-amps while avoiding the life taking h-amps. Madness crept further across her face, broad in both smile and contempt. The system's alarms screamed for once causing her pleasure, not pain.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Self Care</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/self_care/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Self Care" /><published>2024-09-20T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-09-20T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/self_care</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/self_care/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="tea" /><category term="coffee" /><category term="forest" /><category term="spirit" /><category term="goddess" /><category term="lovely" /><category term="green" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Somedays you just need a break, ya know? Like those days when the squirrels just won't stop chattering, or when the wolves keep needlessly scent marking your fav trees. They are like your BFFs and are alway like, ewe... I HATE it when they do that too me. I mean, you try to lead them away with your compulsory powers, but unlike people, wolves ALWAYS find their way home. Maybe your days don't look quite like mine, but I know, you know, that overly lively , just, ah! So the next time you get tired of your wolves, just sigh... become human and have a cup of tea with me, your lovely next door forest.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Orb’s Trail</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/orbs_trail/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Orb’s Trail" /><published>2024-09-20T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-09-20T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/orbs_trail</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/orbs_trail/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="owl" /><category term="ghost" /><category term="trees" /><category term="forest" /><category term="dark" /><category term="lost" /><category term="soul" /><category term="guide" /><category term="wasted" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do we dream of a peaceful passing? No, most of us don't. If fact, bring up the thought of parashing and many of use fill with dread and fear. Woe so fills our hearts that we plead with whom ever may be there to spare us just another day. We then fill that day with normal activities, until we settle and forget once again the fragility of our existance. Others embrace the thought of mortality, using the idea to spur on decisions our conscious is not well fond of. You only live once after all. The fact is, no matter if we display our ignorance of death by forgetting its existance or down playing its possibility, we should all long for a peaceful passing. One where our soul can become whole and move beyond our past. Here lies the sad truth, no amout of contemplation, meditation, or foresight will ever guarentee an ideal death. Evil lurks to keep us shackeled, bewildered, and searching in this world. Keeping a ghostly presence here to echo the voice and intention of this evil. Still others seek to guide the lost, to help them find the peace they have become in such dire need of. Their forms and trails may show different light, but to the unease of such orbs they act as their white knight.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Onironauta</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/onironauta/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Onironauta" /><published>2024-09-20T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-09-20T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/onironauta</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/onironauta/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="pink" /><category term="girl" /><category term="old" /><category term="master" /><category term="psycodelic" /><category term="storm" /><category term="tree" /><category term="mushroom" /><category term="two" /><category term="headed" /><category term="goat" /><category term="horse" /><category term="cloak" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wondering on a lost trail along the recesses of her mind, a girl ponders her existance. Does walk among a dream of her own, or is she a mear figment. The play thing of some distant being watching her every move play out on his grand stage. Giving her subtle nudges. A left here, a right their, walk slowly around the bend. She feels like she has little control over any path she might take. Slipping into cognitave fuzz, each passing step feels a little less. A right here, a left there, lean forward against the resistance of the hill. Soon she frees in a total trance, completely uninhibited by healthy congative function. It proves to blissful to last. With her last heavy blink, her senses shock to life. A despirate, yet sweet cry wallows in the grass along her path. A small creature, familure, but oh, wildly different. A second head he had. One carefree and brash, to bring antics to her life. The other sweet and subdued, to prevent her from becoming too crude. The one with wild mane says 'Take the path forward, untold riches lie ahead'. The other, whose ears settle low, says'Take the path back, only safety is known from where you return.' Unknowning what to do the girl ponders for what feels like hours. Should I listen to you, oh free spirit, who promises a life of abondon and untold comfort. Or should I listen to you, oh cautious one, so faithful and true, offering contentment in what I already know. Like two tormenting children, their voice ring in her head, paralyzing her will to move ahead. The topic of choice circles, over and over, until she can hear of it no more. 'You only look forward, to your next thrill or your erragant desires. And you only look back, to your bitter knowledge and selfish fears. For now I am running back, but only to a new road!' She runs and runs, fighting the storms of her life. Will they catch her? No, but the monsters just might!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Mutant Hide and Seek</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/mutant_hide_and_seek/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mutant Hide and Seek" /><published>2024-09-20T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-09-20T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/mutant_hide_and_seek</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/mutant_hide_and_seek/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="mutant" /><category term="poem" /><category term="stench" /><category term="smell" /><category term="noise" /><category term="mishmash" /><category term="beast" /><category term="mythical" /><category term="moon" /><category term="heroine" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Diurnoct's forest, where moonbeams play, A mystical realm teems with fungal sway, Insects dance, and ruins whisper tales of old, Amidst this wonder, a nuisance growing bold. Meet the beast of mishmash might, Lion's mane, horse's body, crow's feet in sight, Cow's gentle head, rabbit ears so fine, Three blue-green eyes gleam, but oh, the stench divine! Night's cacophony, its righteous ear-piercing call, Keeps villagers awake, if one then all. Enter our heroine, with spirit bright, Playful and mischievous, in the moon's pale light, She seeks to protect her home dear, With a plan to drive the beast away, no fear! No traps or harm, just wit and guile, To outsmart the creature, with a gentle smile. Armed with forest knowledge, and a heart so light, She approaches the beast, on this moon-kissed night, Offering treats, and a gentle, guiding hand, Dear mishmash friend, she says, let's find a new land. The beast, surprised by kindness, true and rare, Follows the girl, with an awkward, lovable air. Beyond the forest edge, a gentle river's flow, Together they wander, through Diurnoct's glow. Until the creature finds a new home, Far, far away from the villager's moan. Beaming a grin, our heroine returns, with victory and delight, Her heart full of cheer, in the silent, moonlit night. Now the village, so sleepy, may rest its weary head, Bearing eyes, so heavy, may finaly go to bed! For though the beast was bothersome, and quite a test, Her heartwarming solution, proved kindness is always best.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Little Charm</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/little_charm/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Little Charm" /><published>2024-09-20T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-09-20T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/little_charm</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/little_charm/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="anglerfish" /><category term="dark" /><category term="light" /><category term="mermaid" /><category term="ocean" /><category term="soul" /><category term="lost" /><category term="suffering" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many find fascination in dreaming of and studying monsters of the deep. However, not all monsters are born of flesh and bone. Tremondous spirits lurk amongst the depths, seeking to feast on the souls lost to the dreadful ocean tides. At first, they extend an offer of guiding hope to voyagers removed from body. An brilliant light from a little charm, visible only to the departed, percing the abyss. It entrances the souls with a promise of an end to their suffering journey, one which, in many cases, has lasted traversed for years. No previously living sapient is entirely immume to undertaking the journey or the promise of its end. When near the light, the unwilling soul experiences a great swell from behind. Possessed by abandoning fear, they grasp towards their false savior, still believeing in the object of their damnation. The swell proves too powerful to fight, and no soul, living or dead, can save them from their choices. In the end, there is Little Charm, their guide to eternal nothingness.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Brox The Defiant</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/brox_the_defiant/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Brox The Defiant" /><published>2024-09-20T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-09-20T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/brox_the_defiant</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/brox_the_defiant/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="slave" /><category term="bald" /><category term="ripped" /><category term="strong" /><category term="chains" /><category term="bone" /><category term="skeletal" /><category term="red" /><category term="ferocious" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some men train their bodies for the most excruitiating of physical tasks by choice, mostly to prove their exemplary masculinity. Other men have their bodies trained for them, so that they are not just a slave to their masters, but also a slave to their own body. In times past slaves were kept weak for fear of strong slaves leading a rebellion. However, due to a great equalization in power thanks to ranged weapons, great physicalliy adds little to one's personal power. Brox is one such person possessing brutal strength not by his own choice. He is no greater than a dog fighting for his master's gain and whimsy, and only feigns to the crowd a better position. However, the spirit in Brox has not diminished. He knows it is the only aspect of his life that is freely his own, and he continues on in hopes to one day serve a future brighter than his own.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Arctechnic Wonderer</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/arctechnic_wonderer/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Arctechnic Wonderer" /><published>2024-09-20T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-09-20T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/artechnic_wonderer</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/arctechnic_wonderer/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="ice" /><category term="arctic" /><category term="witch" /><category term="seal" /><category term="light" /><category term="aurora" /><category term="lantern" /><category term="city" /><category term="tundra" /><category term="lantern" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most people shrink from the idea of living in an area where all soil is foreign ground. A place where the annual high temperature rarely exceeds that of frozen water by more than a few degrees. Yet, some individuals, driven by desperation or a unique vision, seek to this place to create paradise. Over many years of settlement, new arts have sprouted amidst the barren backdrop, much like seedlings nourished by the struggles of their people. Some of these arts shape the culture, bringing joy amidst the bitter surroundings. Others shape daily life and struggle, aiming to make tomorrow a bit easier. The culmination of these artistic and technological advancements is found at the capital city's Arctechnic Institute, dedicated to advancing this free people's paradise. In one of the Arctechnic Institute's study tracks, it is customary for students and professors to periodically demonstrate their mastery of life on the frozen terrain. This practice is of great interest to those who wish to test new equipment designs, validate environmental theories, or gain a deeper understanding of their harsh surroundings. Like many adventurers, they return with stories of love and loss, of great heroics or immense tragedy. Some pack out or even adorn artifacts from their excursions as proof of their tales, exaggerated or not. Among the favored study sites are the open-pit volcanoes that dot the interior of the wasteland. These rare warm spots attract astonishing numbers of flora and fauna, drawing both researchers and traders. The most captivating creatures drawn to these volcanic oases are the seals of light (loosely translated from the local dialect). These translucent beings shimmer with an ethereal glow, their bodies pulsating with light which mirrors the lava pools below. They are entirely dependent on external sources of heat and light for survival, thriving in the unique microclimates around the volcanoes. The seals of light have become an integral part of life in this frozen landscape. Their presence is not just a testament to nature's resilience, but also a symbol of hope and adaptability for the settlers. In harsh environs, where every resource must be carefully managed, these creatures offer a sustainable solution. During expeditions, Arctechnic wonderers often carry special lanterns which cast an especially enticing volcanic glow. The seals of light find this most alluring, so they tend to gather near. At night, around campfires, the translucent bodies of the seals create a mesmerizing display of soft, dancing shadows on the snow anor ice. In modern times, traveling with seals of light has become commonplace. These translucent beings are not only a source of sustenance but also a symbol of the deep connection between the people and the area they have chosen to call home. As travelers journey through the frozen wasteland, the seals of light serve as guides, leading them to the warm oases that sustain natural life in this harsh environment.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Causal Sophist</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/the_causal_sophist/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Causal Sophist" /><published>2024-09-20T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-09-20T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/the_causal_sophist</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/the_causal_sophist/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="philosopher" /><category term="stars" /><category term="universe" /><category term="flow" /><category term="ponder" /><category term="silk" /><category term="power" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA['Like many things, it is a manner of causal findings. The infinite space in the universe facilitates the requirements of the stars. Therefore, the stars are present. If the needs of the start were unmet in this universe, surely our children would not be able to take them in their wondrous gaze each and every night.' Teachings like these make up the core foundation of the philosophy of the Causal Sophist. Generally, the reach of her pondering is far too great for her meager, human understanding. Still, these musings take many lesser minds to places they could not dare to reach on their own. In every right, she is a genius, so few can spot the subtle flaws present in her propositions. Those who can, however, are left feeling like not much has actually been presented. Still, both her and her most devoted followers are claimed to possess mastery of supernatural powers stemming from her other worldly oneness with the expansive minds flowing through the universe.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tira Marvelous Myriad</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/tira_marvelous_myriad/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tira Marvelous Myriad" /><published>2024-07-04T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-07-04T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/tira_marvalous_mirad</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/tira_marvelous_myriad/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sky" /><category term="hands" /><category term="build" /><category term="machine" /><category term="wand" /><category term="red" /><category term="industrial" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tira is one of many mechanics employed to build and maintain high atmosphere launch platforms connecting to blue-red shift columns close to Kipukas space. Tira is exemplary, however. Not only does she take it upon her self to learn the complete plans of a project before execution, but she obsessively tailors her personal gear to fit its most miniscule details. This has resulted in a vast collection of fantastic devices which she employs with marvelous skill. As she works, the movements between her body and gear blend flawlessly. Whether positioning herself precariously to reach the bolt that no one else is daring enough to fasten, unabashedly jumping from scaffold to scaffold to be the first on the next project (or in the lunch line), or fending off would be pirates she presents a kind of intangible grace. Because of this, her colleagues often say she is an angel with talent instead of wings.]]></summary></entry></feed>