<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-06-15T22:25:30-06:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Kipukas</title><subtitle>Welcome to the Kipukas Card Binder! Here you will find all of the cards that make up Kipukas as well as some important info regarding game play. This site will remain free (as in beer) to use always as it is intended to enhance the game experiance, not lock you into a pay to play system. Our online shop is in active development at kipukas.us where you can find more info and make purchases. If desired, you can always email us with issues or order requests. Enjoy the site!</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Gray Wolf: Harbinger of Night</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/gray_wolf_harbinger_of_night/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Gray Wolf: Harbinger of Night" /><published>2024-06-07T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-06-07T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/gray_wolf_harbinger_of_night</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/gray_wolf_harbinger_of_night/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="wolf" /><category term="howling" /><category term="forest" /><category term="rock" /><category term="edge" /><category term="cliff" /><category term="moon" /><category term="night" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Living on most of the world's continents, wolfs have fascinated people for centuries adapting their way into our hearts and homes. While most zoologists know the wolf's howl as a means of communication among their pack, some decided this was not enough. They sought to create the god our ancestors imagined them to be, gods of the night under the moon. Unlike normal gray wolves, these fervently praise the moon with their howls, thereby raising their collective mental state in exultance.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hidden Portal of Lower Dreadmont Cave</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/hidden_portal_of_lower_dreadmont_cave/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hidden Portal of Lower Dreadmont Cave" /><published>2024-06-07T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-06-07T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/hidden_portal_of_lower_dreadmont_cave</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/hidden_portal_of_lower_dreadmont_cave/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="cave" /><category term="mystical" /><category term="skull" /><category term="dragon" /><category term="explorer" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hiding deep within caverns of Dreadmont exists a gateway whence great power dwells. Few creatures have the means to survive the journey through the disorienting web-work passages, the ensnaring crevices, and sudden cliffs to reach the lower cave system. In the lower system there are fewer passages to follow, but horizontal points of rest become scarce. New treacherous obstacles such as rarified air displaced by toxic gases and water filled chambers join the effort to stave off explorers. Somewhere, miles below the surface, stands a tall cavern normally waiting in pitch black. However, when a skilled spelunker finds the cave with a heart open to receive the power and consequence dwelling beyond, a searing light emerges. Should the weary soul pass the final life binding test, they will find themselves past through the gate in a state beyond contestation.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Myrthvither Raven</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/myrthvither_raven/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Myrthvither Raven" /><published>2024-06-07T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-06-07T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/myrthvither_raven</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/myrthvither_raven/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="raven" /><category term="plant" /><category term="flower" /><category term="thorns" /><category term="crow" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Myrthvither Raven is a constantly moving and easily adapts to new environments. It possesses a wicked intelligence and tends to be quite self serving. Often, these ravens know several languages and can effectively communicate between species. Imbued with foliage near death, they easily disguise themselves in natural environments. They act as nearly perfect scouts, if offered a strong enough incentive to put themselves at risk. Many request exotic ant species as payment. Their intent with this behavior is unclear, however, some have observed ants living within their plant mass, a likely sign of a symbiotic relationship.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Neural Network Synapse Virus</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/neural_network_synapse_virus/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Neural Network Synapse Virus" /><published>2024-06-07T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-06-07T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/neural_network_synapse_virus</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/neural_network_synapse_virus/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="node" /><category term="block" /><category term="brain" /><category term="synapse" /><category term="computer" /><category term="lines" /><category term="web" /><category term="neuron" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of a class of virus designed to infect and interrupt the neural network. Subtle in design and task, the synapse virus is designed to inject itself from an infected host network into a model in training. By applying slight changes to the matrix, the virus undercuts the sensical responses an AI provides in response to environmental input. This virus has no meaning of existence.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Enchantress of Cats</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/enchantress_of_cats/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Enchantress of Cats" /><published>2023-12-21T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2023-12-21T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/entrantress_of_cats</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/enchantress_of_cats/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="cave" /><category term="cats" /><category term="witch" /><category term="old" /><category term="lady" /><category term="fire" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many have heard the rumors. Some have seen the fearsome creatures, but few have survived when met ankle to face with the black cat. Still fewer are those born to charm, entertain, and serve the spirits within. Among these leagues are those so in tune with the beasts that they win the beasts acclaim, no that's too strong, tolerance. These enchantresses even force the creatures to mind, sorry no, occasionally sway their opinion of what needs to be done. If you have experience with these creatures, you know the terror the enchantresses must inflict to get that type of response. Meow... ahhh!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Losetany Steppes</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/losetany_steppes/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Losetany Steppes" /><published>2023-12-21T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2023-12-21T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/losetany_steppes</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/losetany_steppes/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="jellyfish" /><category term="landscape" /><category term="camp" /><category term="yurt" /><category term="cloud" /><category term="night" /><category term="wonderer" /><category term="ruins" /><category term="statue" /><category term="mountains" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This kipuka contains many expansive grasslands and wastelands. For the people living here, it is considered a right of passage to survive a journey carrying their village token to the wizened elder. To complete their task they must face a walk through endless miles of grasslands, followed by a guided crossing beyond the regions tallest peak, and finished with a 3 day trek trough the wastes. After setting out with unsure glee, one of the tribe's young girls, Doran, just completed the first leg of her journey after finding the guide's camp near calumniator ruinas. Almost as a sign of her inevitable success, a bloom of the Cumulon jellyfish fills the night sky. Their waving lappets give Doran the sense that the creatures want to greet her into the the next chapters of her life. As she looks upon the glowing wisps of vapor, calm and reassurance wash over Doran. Now she can prepare for the next difficult steps of her journey.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ushered Through Sabina Emporium</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/ushered_through_sabina_emporium/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ushered Through Sabina Emporium" /><published>2023-12-21T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2023-12-21T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/ushered_through_sabina_emporium</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/ushered_through_sabina_emporium/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="crowd" /><category term="dragon" /><category term="skeleton" /><category term="manner" /><category term="shop" /><category term="mall" /><category term="detailed" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A battle between ancestry and heritage rages. In attempts to prove their hold on the future, fathers and sons spill the blood of each. The knowledge of what builds the future, our present, dissipates from the warriors' conscious. In its place rises the focus to triumph, skewing the edges of internal right and wrong. Before the future is lost to those with brave and foolish hearts, angels intervened with pleas for mercy. Selflessly running between the projectiles, their wives and daughters had called back the warriors' hearts to reality. The first daughter to demonstrate her courage, Sabina, died under bloody cloth. In her honor, a temple and a steeple were constructed upon the spot of her death. As often happens to grand buildings over the passing times, they become repurposed to suit the modern culture. In this case, Sabina's temple found bustling life as it transformed to its region's largest emporium. While luring to tourists, the emporium proves a glorious nest for scammers and thieves. Some find hidden jewels, archaeological treasures, or historical tomes while others find rubbish, malice, and sometimes death. Still, It has been said that when one casts their gaze to the sky beyond the vaulted glass they will feel overwhelmed with the courage of Sabina.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Balanced Inline Processing Colony</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/balanced_inline_processing_colony/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Balanced Inline Processing Colony" /><published>2023-09-05T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-09-05T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/balanced_inline_processing_colony</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/balanced_inline_processing_colony/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="brick" /><category term="color" /><category term="chip" /><category term="computer" /><category term="lightning" /><category term="processor" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Biochemists, tasked by a group of descendants in Indochina, designed a bacterium capable of transmitting electric signals around the cell wall to their colony through the cell's pilus (hair-like appendages). These were then coxed into bacterial arrays capable of enduring higher currents. All of this was with the intent of producing full-fledged micro-processors capable of storing data without the use of any metal in order to smuggle secrets into communist China. The first iteration of the project, though prohibitively expensive, proved successful without the governments determining foul play. The agents responsible for delivering the devices proved to be the weak point of the process. Many got caught, due to repeat travel, while others were incapable maintaining the conditions sufficient for the chip's survival. Due to the touchy nature of the chip's survival, data was never captured and the project lived on. Some wonder if these colonies are capable of self awareness.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Incubation Egg</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/incubation_egg/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Incubation Egg" /><published>2023-09-05T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-09-05T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/incubation-egg</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/incubation_egg/"><![CDATA[<div x-data="{ play_data: true }" class="z-30 w-11/12 md:w-2/3 xl:w-1/2 pb-2 place-self-center">
  <p class="capitalize" >
    card variation
  </p>
  <div x-show="play_data" class="mt-1 h-0.5 w-1/2 bg-kip-red lg:bg-slate-400 justify-self-center"></div>
  <div x-show="play_data" class="mt-1 h-0.5 w-full bg-slate-200 lg:bg-kip-red"></div>
  <p x-show="play_data" class="text-center">
    
    
      Non-Playable
      
      
    
  </p>
</div>

<div x-data="{ play_data: true }" class="z-30 w-11/12 md:w-2/3 xl:w-1/2 pb-2 place-self-center">
  <p class="capitalize" >
    Scarcity
  </p>
  <div x-show="play_data" class="mt-1 h-0.5 w-1/2 bg-kip-red lg:bg-slate-400 justify-self-center"></div>
  <div x-show="play_data" class="mt-1 h-0.5 w-full bg-slate-200 lg:bg-kip-red"></div>
  <p x-show="play_data" class="text-center">
    
    
      Untamed
      
      
    
  </p>
</div>

<div x-data="{ play_data: true }" class="z-30 w-11/12 md:w-2/3 xl:w-1/2 pb-2 place-self-center">
  <p class="capitalize" >
    History
  </p>
  <div x-show="play_data" class="mt-1 h-0.5 w-1/2 bg-kip-red lg:bg-slate-400 justify-self-center"></div>
  <div x-show="play_data" class="mt-1 h-0.5 w-full bg-slate-200 lg:bg-kip-red"></div>
  <p x-show="play_data" class="text-center">
    
    
      Eggs are delicious or precious, but definitely vulnerable. They represent the next generation for many species and always need diligent protection. This is your task. The Incubation Egg is a super special Kipukas card. Rather than being playable, it represents your stake in the future. This card is your proof of eligibility for the rarest cards of our next generation. This allows access to the rarest card categories, normally reserved for competition winners and special event giveaways, if you are willing to wait out a long incubation period. After the incubation time, ship this card back to us and will ship you the 'hatchling'. Check Building Decks: Incubation cards for more information.
      
      
    
  </p>
</div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="egg" /><category term="warhol" /><category term="andy" /><category term="special" /><category term="cubic" /><category term="brick" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eggs are delicious or precious, but definitely vulnerable. They represent the next generation for many species and always need diligent protection. This is your task. The Incubation Egg is a super special Kipukas card. Rather than being playable, it represents your stake in the future. This card is your proof of eligibility for the rarest cards of our next generation. This allows access to the rarest card categories, normally reserved for competition winners and special event giveaways, if you are willing to wait out a long incubation period. After the incubation time, ship this card back to us and will ship you the 'hatchling'. Check Building Decks: Incubation cards for more information.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Knightsoul of Binding Time</title><link href="https://www.kipukas.cards/knightsoul_of_binding_time/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Knightsoul of Binding Time" /><published>2023-09-05T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-09-05T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://www.kipukas.cards/knightsoul_of_binding_time</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.kipukas.cards/knightsoul_of_binding_time/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="triple" /><category term="infinity" /><category term="knight" /><category term="sword" /><category term="sir" /><category term="regal" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[In search for the revival of the ways of old, a small group of zealots held fervent meetings in order to connect with spirits holding the lives they desired. Hundreds of years passed with little but enormous ancestral faith to show for their desires, calls, and pleas. None lost hope, ardent and steadfast that one day they would stand rewarded. One frigged night, their leader woke from a transcendental, all consuming dream, claiming to have met the one they sought. 'A knight covered in blue. Bound by all that has past at the foot, one who sees what has never passed, and encompasses all that is now. It came. We have always known of the higher society; now I have seen it.' Many others now claim visits from the Knightsoul, and some say it has passed them edicts. While the existence of the Knightsoul hasn't been confirmed, the people's passionate belief won't be denied.]]></summary></entry></feed>